<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[Groupclone Feeds]]></title>
    <link>http://www.groupclone.net</link>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 07:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <generator>Zend_Feed</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[$15 for $30 Worth of Paint-Your-Own Pottery and Glass Fusing at Studio 6 Pottery]]></title>
      <link>http://localhost/sales1/deal/$15-for-$30-Worth-of-Paint-Your-Own-Pottery-and-Glass-Fusing-at-Studio-6-Pottery.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Crafting your way into someone's cupboard is the craftiest way into their heart: for $15, you get $30 toward pottery painting and glass fusing at Studio 6 Pottery. The cozy studio in Ocoee welcomes all ages and experience levels.
Studio 6's cheerful pottery palace is a great place to get friends together for a small ceramics gathering, ceramics rave, or first ceramics date rave.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Expires Jan 14, 2011 Limit 1 per person. Limit 1 per table, 2 per table of 4 or more. Dine-in only. Not valid toward happy hour or with other offers. Tax and gratuity not included. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Active Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://localhost/sales1/media/catalog/product/i/m/img.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Get $900 worth of iphone for just $800]]></title>
      <link>http://localhost/sales1/deal/Get-$900-worth-of-iphone-for-just-$800.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People have been dreaming about video calling for decades. iPhone 4 makes it a reality. With the tap of a button, you can wave hello to your kids, share a smile from across the globe, or watch your best friend laugh at your stories &mdash; iPhone 4 to iPhone 4 over Wi-Fi. No other phone makes staying in touch this much fun.

iPhone 4 has two built-in cameras, one on the front above the display and one on the back next to the LED flash. The front camera has been tuned for FaceTime. It has just the right field of view and focal length to focus on your face at arm&rsquo;s length. So it always presents you in the best possible light.Imagine your sister is away at school and can&rsquo;t make it to your son&rsquo;s birthday. So you&rsquo;re cheering her up with a FaceTime call. As the cupcakes come out, your son&rsquo;s eyes light up, and you just have to share it. Tap a button, and before you can say, &ldquo;Make a wish,]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Expires Jan 14, 2011 Limit 1 per person. Limit 1 per table, 2 per table of 4 or more. Dine-in only. Not valid toward happy hour or with other offers. Tax and gratuity not included. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Active Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://localhost/sales1/media/catalog/product/i/p/iphone_0412_2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[$350 for $500 worth of New Model Tshirt]]></title>
      <link>http://localhost/sales1/deal/$350-for-$500-worth-of-New-Model-Tshirt.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton's presidential campaign may be dead, but she's determined to see this t-shirt contest thing through to the end. After receiving "almost 5,000 amazing entries" and more than 125,000 online votes, the contest has picked a winner (pictured at left). Designed by "Denitza of Weehawken, New Jersey" (which sounds like a circa-1930s purveyor of charming ladies' chapeaux), the winning design is heavy on the text. Set in a Matt Groening-flavored typeface is the catchy slogan: "For everyone who's ever been counted out but refused to be knocked out and for everyone who works hard but never gives up, this one [insert silhouette of Hillary, standing at attention in a pantsuit and kitten heels] is for you!" The "limited-edition t-shirt" can be yours for a $50 contribution, which will go toward paying down Hillary's campaign debt. As for the design, noted Hillary in a letter to supporters, "it won by a landslide.
Get a jump on the day with Mediabistro's Morning Media Newsfeed. We'll send you an email before 9 am with fifteen stories that everyone in the industry should know about before they get to work.We cover everything from breaking updates on major media deals to think pieces from journals you wouldn't usually check out.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Expires Jan 14, 2011 Limit 1 per person. Limit 1 per table, 2 per table of 4 or more. Dine-in only. Not valid toward happy hour or with other offers. Tax and gratuity not included. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Side Deal</category>
      <category>Active Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://localhost/sales1/media/catalog/product/t/s/tshirt_3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[One HOTT Deal A Day Coming Your Way! ]]></title>
      <link>http://localhost/sales1/deal/One-HOTT-Deal-A-Day-Coming-Your-Way!.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One HOTT deal a day for Restaurants, Bars/Clubs, Spas, Salons, Parks and Recreation, Retail, and Entertainment.  Deal Me One is out to find you the best possible option for your hard earned dollar.
1) We start by hunting down the best deals in your area
2) We offer the Deal at the best possible price and exclusively for Deal Me One customers
3) As long as we reach the minimum number of Deal Me One buyers everyone gets the benefits of the deal. If the deal doesn't reach the sufficient number of buyers your credit cards will NEVER be charged (this is why billing information is processed within 24hrs of the deals closing)
4) Once its a "Done Deal" and your credit card has been charged you will recive a printable "Deal Card" via email
5) Remember to bring your Deal Card and PHOTO ID to the business and ENJOY YOUR DEAL AND DEALS TO COME!]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Expires Jan 14, 2011 Limit 1 per person. Limit 1 per table, 2 per table of 4 or more. Dine-in only. Not valid toward happy hour or with other offers. Tax and gratuity not included. Reservation required.See the rules that apply to all deals.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Side Deal</category>
      <category>Active Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://localhost/sales1/media/catalog/product/i/m/images3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Get $900 worth of Ferrari-599 for just $700.]]></title>
      <link>http://localhost/sales1/deal/Get-$900-worth-of-Ferrari-599-for-just-$700..html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Ferrari 360 is a mid-engine midsize two-seater sports car produced from late 1999 until 2005. The 360 replaced the Ferrari F355 and was itself replaced by the fairly similar Ferrari F430. For the 360, Ferrari partnered with Alcoa to produce an entirely new all-aluminum space-frame chassis that was 40% stiffer than the F355, yet 28% lighter despite a 10% increase in overall dimensions. Along with the new frame was a new Pininfarina  body styling that broke ranks with the last decade's sharp angles and flip-up headlights, replacing them with a rounded appearance that harkened to the 1960s. The new V8 engine, common to all versions, was only slightly larger and more powerful than the F355's at 3.6 litres and 400 bhp (300 kW) of power, but the lighter frame and added stiffness improved performance; the 0 to 100 km/h (62 mph) acceleration performance improved from 4.6 to 4.4 seconds. An engine replacement resulted in the V8 road model that followed, the F430  (internally referred to as the evoluzione or evo) which came out in 2004.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Expires Jan 14, 2011 Limit 1 per person. Limit 1 per table, 2 per table of 4 or more. Dine-in only. Not valid toward happy hour or with other offers. Tax and gratuity not included. Reservation required.See the rules that apply to all deals.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Side Deal</category>
      <category>Active Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://localhost/sales1/media/catalog/product/f/e/ferrari-599_1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ $49 worth  VX818Mp3 Player $41 Only]]></title>
      <link>http://localhost/sales1/deal/$49-worth--VX818Mp3-Player-$41-Only.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Onda will be launching an Mp3 player that looks much like an eraser you used to use at school. The VX818 features a 1.1 inch OLED display, 1GB/2GB capacities, SRS sound effect and compatible with MP1, MP2, MP3, WMA, WMV, ASF, WAV, OGG formats along with 7EQ modes, multiple playback modes, E-book and U disk functions. The 1GB and 2GB versions]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Expires Jan 14, 2011 Limit 1 per person. Limit 1 per table, 2 per table of 4 or more. Dine-in only. Not valid toward happy hour or with other offers. Tax and gratuity not included. Reservation required.See the rules that apply to all deals.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Side Deal</category>
      <category>Active Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://localhost/sales1/media/catalog/product/d/i/digit-mp3-player-02.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Microsoft handset worth $40 for $30 - Merchant Deal]]></title>
      <link>http://localhost/sales1/deal/Microsoft-handset-worth-$40-for-$30---Merchant-Deal.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This comfortable, high-quality stereo headset gives you the simplicity of USB installation and high-quality digital sound that cannot be matched by analog. Hold clear, private Internet voice calls, enjoy music and movies, and become fully immersed in your games.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Side Deal</category>
      <category>Active Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://localhost/sales1/media/catalog/product/m/i/microsoft_xbox_360_live_wireless_headset.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
